itechpassion.com 2015-06-07

# Privacy Policy Page

Privacy Policy

Privacy of our visitors is very important to us. We don’t share & sell any kind of private information to 3rd party while visiting our website itechpassion.com. We keep your and your family privacy in safeguard.

Routine Information Collection :-

All web servers track basic information about their visitors. This information includes, but is not limited to, IP addresses, browser details, timestamps and referring pages. None of this information can personally identify specific visitors to this site. The information is tracked for routine administration and maintenance purposes.

Cookies and Web Beacons :-

Where necessary, itechpassion.com uses cookies to store information about a visitor’s preferences and history in order to better serve the visitor and/or present the visitor with customized content.

Advertising partners and other third parties may also use cookies, scripts and/or web beacons to track visitors to our site in order to display advertisements and other useful information. Such tracking is done directly by the third parties through their own servers and is subject to their own privacy policies.

How we use collected information :-

I Tech Passion collects and uses Users personal information for the following purposes:

– To personalize user experience

We may use information in the aggregate to understand how our Users as a group use the services and resources provided on our Site.

– To improve our Site

We continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you.

– To improve customer service

Your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs.

– To send periodic emails

The email address Users provide will only be used to respond to their inquiries, and/or other requests or questions.

Third party websites :-

Users may find advertising or other content on our Site that link to the sites and services of our partners,advertisers, sponsors and other third parties. We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our Site. In addition, these sites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link to our Site, is subject to that website’s own terms and policies.

Controlling Your Privacy :-

Note that you can change your browser settings to disable cookies if you have privacy concerns. Disabling cookies for all sites is not recommended as it may interfere with your use of some sites. The best option is to disable or enable cookies on a per-site basis. Consult your browser documentation for instructions on how to block cookies and other tracking mechanisms.

#### Google Adsense :-

Some of the ads may be served by Google. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to Users based on their visit to our Site and other sites on the Internet. DART uses “non personally identifiable information” and does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, etc. You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html.

Changes to this privacy policy :-

I Tech Passion has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will post a notification on the main page of our Site, revise the updated date at the bottom of this page. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.

#### Contact Information :-

Concerns or questions about this privacy policy can be directed to admin@itechpassion.com or use this[ ](http://jbsworldwide.com/test/contact-us/ "Contact Us")[Contact Us ](http://jbsworldwide.com/test/contact-us/ "Contact Us")Form for further clarification.

This document was last updated on April 10,2014.
